1000goals.com 2015-06-23

# Privacy | Football - 1000 Goals

**27 February 2008** at 01:51 GMT

Third Party Advertising:  
We serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third Party Cookies:  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Personal Information:  
This Web site does allow user to enter their email address at their own will for comments on our site. We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. 1000goals.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Latest Football News

Venezuela might be set for a difficult Copa America clash against Brazil this weekend, but La Vinotinto won't be giving up easily as they are keen on getting a ticket into the next round. That ambition was being highlighted by Venezuela head coach, Noel Sanvicente who stated to the media that his side must get…

Colombia are setting up to play their final group game in Copa America against Peru and Jose Pekerman's side are treating that tie as it was a final. That situation was being shouted by Colombia's shot stopper, David Ospina who stated that it will be an important battle and a tough one as well, since Peru…

Uruguay head coach, Oscar Tabarez was quite pleased with the draw his side picked up against Paraguay as the tactician believes that Ramon Diaz's men were a tough opposition. Speaking in a news conference, Tabarez admitted that Paraguay proved they are a difficult team to beat, so in the end that 1-1 draw was quite…

Brazil are gearing up for their final Copa America group game against Venezuela this weekend and ahead of that tie, Selecao head coach, Dunga shared his hope of having his talisman, Neymar back on action. The Barcelona star received hefty punishment for his petulant reaction in Brazil's 1-0 defeat to Colombia with the tournament's disciplinary panel…

Playing fantasy league in any sports have been such popular thing for fans this days, triggering many sites to provide exciting gaming platform such as what Fan Picks is currently offering. This website is giving out a way for fans to enjoy playing fantasy game while earning real money reward for their persistent hard work.…

### Football Scores & Highlights

### Latest Football Highlights
